

+358 404627541



prtyushaduvvuri98@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/pratyushaduvvuri-933040136/

Naga Pratyusha Duvvuri

Dedicated IT professional with extensive experience in software development and support within fastgrowing SaaS environments. Proficient in Java, Python, SQL, and various frameworks and tools. Demonstrated ability to troubleshoot complex issues and provide excellent customer service. Certified in Oracle Cloud and Azure with strong analytical skills and a proactive approach to problem-solving.

Experience

OCTOBER 2023 - APRIL 2024

SCUBI Support Maintenance

- OSB Developer for an employment benefit project for the United States.
- Developed technical documentation and managed SQL databases.
- Created test cases and maintained high-quality code.

FEBRUARY 2021 - JULY 2023

Atradius Project

- Oracle BPM/SOA Developer and Solution Analyst for a trade credit insurance company.
- Integrated services from DB (SQL) to Middleware (SOA, OSB).
- Conducted unit testing with SoapUI and Postman.
- Maintained project files in GitHub.
- Maintained Project Documentation and Reporting

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: Python, SQL, JavaScript

Frameworks: Oracle BPM, Oracle SOA **Operating Systems:** Linux, Windows Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, SQL Server

Tools and IDEs: MSOffice, PyCharm, Eclipse, Visual Studio, Jdeveloper, SoapUI, Postman, GitHub, Jira,

Confluence, Slack

Cloud Platforms: Oracle Cloud, Azure Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript. **DevOps Tools:** GitHub, Jenkins, CI/CD.

Education

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

Pragati Engineering College, Autonomous, India

06/2016 - 09/2020 | Grade: 8.69

Certifications

- Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Foundations 2021
- Oracle Cloud Infrastructure 2024 Generative AI Certified Professional
- Oracle Cloud Infrastructure 2023 Application Integration Professional
- Microsoft Azure Certifications: AZ-900, AZ-104, AZ-400
- NPTEL Certifications in Programming, Data Structures, and Algorithms Using Python, Enhancing Softskills and Personality
- Coursera Certifications in IoT Programming, Advanced Machine Learning with TensorFlow

Personal Projects and Publications

- Accenture North America Data Analytics and Visualization Job Simulation on Forage (May 2024)
 - o Conducted data cleaning, modeling, and analysis for a hypothetical social media client.
 - o Prepared presentations to communicate insights for strategic decision-making.
- Topic: Research on Application of Artificial Intelligence in Medical Education (Data Management Project)
 - Main Project done in Final year: 12/2019 05/2020
 - Software tools: Python, Django
 - o It is Operational Data Management Project.
 - o Through research on application of artificial intelligence in distance medical education
 - This application integrates with Student, Trainer, Admin for sharing information and knowledge by posting and clarifying questions.
 - This will result in faster adoption by healthcare providers by mitigating perceived risk, and start to deliver measurable improvements in patient outcomes and operational efficiency at scale.
- Topic: Spam SMS Filtering using Machine Learning (Data Quality Improvement Project)
 - Mini Project : 02/2019 05/2019
 - The main objective of our approach is to classify the spam SMS messages as soon as it received on the mobile phone, regardless of newly created spam message (zero-hour attack).
- **Journal Publication**: The International Journal of Analytical and Experimental Modal Analysis
 - o Research on the application of Artificial Intelligence in Medical Education.

Soft Skills

- Excellent communication and listening skills
- Proactive and adaptable
- Strong problem solving abilities
- Leadership and teamwork capabilities